happening in harvey illinois all right so we're at 144 45 and 144 37 i'm halsted i don't see any
sheriffs here at all no sheriffs here and they boarding these apartments up there's still people
in these apartments there's people living here with their kids section 8 is paying their rent
still and they is putting these people out their house or boarding them up harvey is not the
sheriffs harvey has no control over this they're not the sheriffs y'all is here with no sheriffs
y'all boarding people up in their cribs i'm calling the news i'm calling the lawyers this is so wrong
on so many levels y'all can't do this y'all's not the sheriff y'all don't have the right
there's old people living here there's people living here with their kids that section 8
is paying their rent still and y'all is boarding people up in their cribs they boarding people up
in their houses oh yeah yeah there's an old man boarded up in this apartment right here there's
someone still in this apartment how he gonna get out how is he gonna get out they think harvey
police is allowed to do this they are not the sheriffs i'm trying to understand when did we become
a people so bereft of even just like common decency that we would board up in a goddamn building simply
because somebody told us to like i don't think i was raised so differently that i could see like
yeah even if motherfuckers told me to do that and even though i know i have a job and i need to feed my
family this ain't right like that's really where we are motherfuckers like people units and you would
just board it up because you were told to